Guide to the Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) of Durham, NC records, 1894-1992 RL.11616
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Community Outreach, 1965-1988
  - Durham Women's Health Co-op Files, 1965-1980; 1
    - Counseling Articles, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling-general, 1976-1979; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Policies, 1979; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General Clarification Questions for Decision Making, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General Crisis Intervention Model (diagram), 1979; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General "Dimensions of Interpersonal Response" (handouts), 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General Elements of Facilitating Communication, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General The Helping Relationship, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General Steps in Making Decisions, 1979; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- General Suggestions for Handling Telephone Contact with Troubled People, 1975; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- Problem Pregnancy "Abortion as an Alternative", 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- Problem Pregnancy Checklist (What you should know about Pr. Preg. Counseling), 1977; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- Problem Pregnancy "Decision Making", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Counseling Skills- Problem Pregnancy, Dynamics Involved in Counseling Parent who Plans to Keep Child Alone, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Crisis Counseling Session- General Outline & Crisis Intervention Technique, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Crisis Counseling- Suicide, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Diaphragm, 1973; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - DES Fact Sheet, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - DES- Map, 1975-1979; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Diadic Encounters- One Liners, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Dobbs Ferry Medical Group (N.Y.), 1972; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Dr. & Consumer Surveys- Dental, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Dr. & Consumer Surveys- Family Practice/G.P., 1974-1977; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Dr. & Consumer Surveys- OB/GYN, 1974-1977; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Drug Action of Wake County Crisis Center-Forms, n.d. (Box 61)
    - "Drugs and Devices" IWY Fact Sheet, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Drug Use/Misuse, 1974-1979; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham Women's Center Newsletter- YWCA, 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham Women's Health Cooperative: Meeting Minutes, 1976-1980; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham: Government, Schools Contacts, 1976-1978; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham YMCA Women's Health Cooperative- Counselor Training Announcement, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham YMCA Women's Health Cooperative: Members Information Sheets, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Durham YMCA Women's Health Cooperative: Phone Log, 1979-1981; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - East Gate Medical & Surgical Group, 1972-1977; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - East Side Medical Group (NY), 1972; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Eastern Women's Center (NY), 1972-1975; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Elderly- Articles, 1975-1978; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - ERA, 1978; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Fayetteville-Carolina Women's Health Clinic, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Fertility & Infertility, 1974-1978; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Finances & Credit for Women in USA, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Funding Proposal Material, 1971-1976; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Gynecological Health IWY Fact Sheet, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Care Facilities, 1976-1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Co-op Flyers, 1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Co-op Flyers, Info Sheets, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Co-op Membership List, 1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Co-op New Members-"Welcome" Sheets, n.d. (Box 62)
    - Health Fairs, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Right Issues, 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Health Right Women's Health Forum, 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Herpes II, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - High Blood Pressure, 1975; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Hillcrest Abortion Clinic (D.C.), 1972; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Homosexuality, 1974-1980; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Hospice; Death & Dying, 1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Human Sexual Response, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Human Sexual Response Cycles, 1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Hysterectomy, 1974; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Information Kit- Women's Medical Center, 1972-1975; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - "It's Your Body" sheets, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Law (esp. W/ abortion), 1975-1980; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Local Women's Organizations, 1974-1978; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Maps Richmond, Va Washington, D.C., 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Margaret Sanger Ctr.- Planned Parenthood (New York), 1972-1977; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Menopause, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Menstrual Cycle, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Menstrual Extraction, 1977; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Menstruation, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Mental Health- Providers' & Consumers' Forms, 1974; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Mental Health: Reports Pamphlets, 1978-1980; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Mental Health Law Project Summary of Activities, 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Midwifery & Out-of-Hospital Birthing, 1978-1980; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Monsey Medical Center (NY), 1972; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Morning-After Pill, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - NARAL Newsletter Nat'l Abortion Rights Action League-1, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - NARAL Newsletter Nat'l Abortion Rights Action League-2, 1974-1980; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - National Assn. Of Abortion Facilities (NAAF), 1976; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Nat'l Assn. Of Parents & Professionals for Safe Alternatives in Childbirth (NAPSAC), 1977-1978; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Nestle Boycott/Infant Formula Info-1, 1972-1979; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Nestle Boycott/Infant Formula Info-2, 1974-1979; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - New Summit Medical Center (Washington D.C.), 1976-1978; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - N.Y. Clinics, 1972; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - New York Clinics- Info Sheets, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - NC-Charlotte-Planned Parenthood Clinic, 1974; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Nutrition in general, and for pregnant women, and for babies, 1972-1978; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Occupational Health; NCOSH, ETC, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Other birth control (not pill, IUD) methods, 1972-1978; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Other D.C. Clinics, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Other Women's Periodicals-1, 1976-1979; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Other Women's Periodicals-2, 1975-1979 (Box 64)
    - PEER: Project on Equal Education Rights, 1978-1979; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Pelham Medical Group (N.Y.), 1972; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Perinatal Health Care Programs, 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Physical Health- non-Birth Control Issues, 1963-1979; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1975-1976; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Poetry, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Pregnancy & Childbirth, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Pregnancy Screening, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Pregnancy Testing Saxena, 1975-1978; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Prescriptions, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Preterm-1973 Washington D.C., 1972-1973; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Preterm-1977 Washington D.C., 1976-1977; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - PreBirth Clinic (D.C.), 1972; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Preterm (D.C.), 1971-1976; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Prostaglandins, 1972; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Provider & Consumer Surveys- Clinics, Specialists, Abortion Clinics, 1974-1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - "R.A." N 73 10/2/68, 1968; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Rape, 1975-1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Rewrites, 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Richmond Medical Ctr. For Women, 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Self-Help/Self Health Workshops, 1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Sex ED. Info, Plans, Proposals, Resources, Articles, etc., 1975-1980; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Sexuality, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Siecus, 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Single Parenting: "Practical Considerations for Single Women...", 1976; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Statistics, 1976-1980; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Sterilization (Vasectomy, Laparoscopy, etc.), 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
      Includes information about forced sterilization of African American, Hispanic, and Native American women.
    - Successful Marriage, 1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Summit Medical Center (Washington D.C.), 1972-1973; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Training Handouts- Policy, 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Vaginal Infections, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Vaginitis, cystitis, 1972-1973; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - VD counseling- Training Handouts, 1975-1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - VD Info & Herpes, 1970-1974; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Volunteer Counselors, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Washington Heights Medical Service Group, D.C., 1976-1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Washington Hospital Center Women's Clinic (DC), 1973-1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - W.A.T.C.H. Tallahassee Feminist Women's Health Center, 1976-1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - WHC History File (addresses, lists, etc.), 1975-1977; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Wholistic Health Center, 1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Women and Chronic Diseases: Reducing Risk Factors, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Women & their Bodies Committee, 1973-1974; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Women's Center Women's Groups Support Groups, CR Groups, 1977-1979; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Center YWCA, 1979-1980; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Health Teaching Group Breast Self-Exam- Teaching Guide, 1978; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Health Teaching Group Discussion Guide, 1978; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Health Teaching Group General, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Health Teaching Group Pelvic Exam- Teaching Refresher, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Woman's Hospital St. Luke's Hospital Center, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Medical Center (D.C.), 1974-1978; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Pavilion & Raleigh's Women's Health Organization, 1975-1979; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Women's Services (Center for Reproductive & Sexual Health, Inc.) (NY), 1971-1972; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - YMCA Info Sheets, 1978; 1 folders (Box 66)
  - Rape Crisis Center Subject Files, 1966-1988; 2
    - Acquaintance/Date Rape: Awareness & Prevention, 1982; 1 folders (Box 67)
      The Rape Crisis Center of Durham became part of the Durham YWCA in the early 1980s. It provided counseling and response to victims of sexual abuse, assault and rape. There is also information about other organizations in North Carolina who support or treat victims of sexual violence who are of any age. The subseries notably includes information about various populations who may be at particular risk of experiencing sexual violence, including people with disabilities or children. The subseries includes administrative files, secondary research, handouts, pamphlets, and newspaper clippings.
    - Acquaintance/Date Rape: "Is Dating Dangerous?", 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Acquaintance/Date Rape: "Rape Even- Among Friends", 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Acquaintance/Date Rape: "Terri and Jr. Talk to Teens", 1986; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Acquaintance/Date Rape: "Trust with Caution.", 1988; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adolescent Abuse and Neglect: Intervention Strategies, 1980; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adolescent Rape: Burgess, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adolescent Rape: Case Studies, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adolescent Rape: Otey, 1983; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Advocacy: Children and Law, 1976; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Advocacy: And Sexual Assault, 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: For Others "For Husbands, Fathers, Friends.", 1984; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "It's OK To Ask For Help.", 1986; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: Males, n.d. (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "Men Against Rape", 1977; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: Prevention and Treatment, 1983; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: Rape Awareness, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "Rape... It Can Happen To You", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "What Every Woman Should Know.", 1975; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: What To Do In Case of Sexual Assault, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "What To Do If You Are Raped.", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Sexual Assault: "Your Future... In Your Hands.", 1983; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Survivors: "About Adults Abused As Kids.", 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Adult Survivors: "Recovering... Healing Your Sexuality", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Aftermath Project, 1977; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Baby Love, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Baby Love/Teens., 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Battered Women's Coalition, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Careline, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Clearinghouse on Child Abuse and Neglect Information, 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Council on the Status of Women, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Duke Caps, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Duke Pisces, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Duke Psychology Clinic, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Duke Student Rape Services, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Durham Community Guidance Clinic for Children and Youth, 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Family Counseling Service of Durham, INC., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Family Support Network of NC, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: The Fleming Center, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Guardian Ad Liem, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: HCA Holly Hill, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Lincoln Community Health Center, Durham, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: National Child Rights Alliance, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Parent to Parent, 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Pregnancy Support Services, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: The Rainbow Project, INC., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: RCC Asheville, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: RCC Charlotte, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: RCC Greensboro, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: RCC Orange Co., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: RCC Raleigh, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: The Relatives, INC., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Rougemont/Bahama Health Clinic, 1979; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Structure House, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Trinity House, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: UNC-CH Rape Awareness/ Assistance, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: Watts Group Practice, 1979; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: WIC, 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agencies: The Women's Center, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agency: Durham Co. Social Services, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agency: Parent Aides, 1984; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Agency: Victim's Assistance, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Assertiveness: Students Alberti and Emmons., 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Assertiveness Training: Teens, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Pops: Alcohol. "ABC's of Drinking and Driving.", 1971; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Pops: Alcohol. "About Alcoholism.", 1966; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Pops: Alcohol. "Alcoholic in the Family?", 1977; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Pops: Alcohol. "What Everyone Should Know.", 1973; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Pops: Alcohol. "What Every Teenager Should Know.", 1980; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - At Risk Populations: Alcoholism., 1987; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Bureau of Justice Statistics: Special Report, 1988; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Burnout: Freudenberger, 1975; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - CED; Adolescents. Developmentally Disabled., 1984-1988; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - CED: Adolescents "Violence in Our Lives: Focus on Rape.", 1977; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Adult Self Protection. "Protect Yourself" Poster., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Acquaintance/Date Rape, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Acquaintance Rape. Film and Discussion Series., 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Acquaintance/Date Rape Questions for Forum, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Acquaintance Rape Training, 1986; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Child Abuse Orange County, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Child Abuse Training. US Dept. Of Health., 1979; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Child/Parent Behavior Change, 1984; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Child Sexual Abuse NCCSW, 1986; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Child Sexual Abuse Prevention, 1983; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Day Care Training, 1986; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED; Demographics for Durham Co., 1988; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Designing a Programme, 1986; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Domestic Violence Prevention, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Group Work Sex-Ed, 1983; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Handouts for Adults. Aquaintance Rape, 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Handouts for Adults Rape Quiz, 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Holly Hill Presentations, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Missing Children "Child Identification Card", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Older Adults, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Parents Prevention of Child Sexual Abuse, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police, Pennsylvania, 1983; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police and Missing Children, 1985; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police Training Chicago, 1981; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police Training Durham, 1988; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police Training Rapport, 1981; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Police Training US Department of Health, 1984; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: Public Awareness/DCPCA, 1986; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: RCC Assessment Raleigh, 1978; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: RCC and Feminism, 1984; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: RCC, Illinois, 1983; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: RCC Training Chapel Hill, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - CED: RCC Volunteers, 1985; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex ED/Male, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex-ED Males, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex-ED Parents, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex-ED Peers, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex-ED Preadolescent., 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Sex-ED Religious, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: Volunteer Training Pennsylvania, 1980; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: YWCA Training. Old Training, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - CED: YWCA Training. Pre-Training., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Abuse: Daycare Selection, 1987; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Abuse: Discipline "What You Should Know...", 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Abuse: Missing Children, 1985; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Development: O-Adolescence, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Development: Sex Play, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Development: Sexuality, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Development: Stages of, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Assault: Assessment, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Definitions, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Family Reaction, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Child "Someone Else Knows...", 1984; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Child "Something Happened to Me", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others "About Neglect", 1984; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others "Child Abuse and You.", 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others "C.S.A. Is Happening.", 1982; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others "What Everyone Should Know...", 1976-1981; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others. "What You Know Can Hurt.", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Others "Who Do They Tell?", 1982; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents, 1987; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents "Child Abuse", n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents "Please, no, not my child", 1985; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents. "Tips to Parents.", 1985; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents "What if your child has been molested", 1978; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Parents "What Parents Should Know...", 1984; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: For Teachers. Reporting Procedures., 1985; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Handicapped, 1983; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Indicators, 1987; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Interviewing, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Military, 1987; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Military Communities, 1980; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Missing Child, 1988; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Model Of, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Mothers Who Protect, 1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Over-View, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Overview, 1978; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Overview/DeVine, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Psychology, 1978; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Report to Congress, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Child Sexual Abuse: Spanish "Sobre El Maltrato... Ninos", 1984; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Affective Identification, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Affective Inventory, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Affective Response, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Approach to Victim Schaefer, 1978; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Children, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Contracting with Client, 1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Door Openers, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Latinas, 1978; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Lesbians, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Counseling: Listening Skills, 1974; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Date Rape: Dr. Joyce Brothers, 1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Date Rape: Men's Viewpoint, 1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Date Rape: Prevention, 1985; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Date Rape: Testimonial, 1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Domestic Violence, 1979-1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Elders, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - ER, 1973; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Feminism: Social Control, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Forensic Evidence: Bite Marks, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Gender: Role Attribution, 1983; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Governor's Commission for the Family: A Report to the Governor, 1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Incest, 1978-1985; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Infant Mortality, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: American Indian Law, 1981; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Court and Victim, 1980; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Crime and Justice Encyclopaedia, 1983; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Defense for the Poor. National, 1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Fair Treatment Bill, 1985; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: G.A.L. Model, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: NC Law, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: NC Law and Children, 1981-1983; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: NC Law Proof, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Opinion on Sleeping Victim, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Police Role, 1974; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Police Role/Child, 1978; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Police Role, Durham, 1987; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Prosecutions Orange County, 1985; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: Supreme Court on Sodomy, 1986; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Legal: System Explanation, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 71)